# Md Faisal Hossain



mdfaisal521@outlook.com



01814366774



linkedin.com/in/md-faisal-878628202



https://faisal413.github.io/profile.com/

### Summary

I am Faisal. And I am game Developer. Experienced Data Entry Operator with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), C# (Programming Language), Adobe Photoshop, HTML( Hyper Text Markup Language), CSS (Cascading Style Sheets), JavaScript and Unity (game engine), & Microsoft Office.

### **Experience**



### 

Unity Technologies Dec 2020 - Present (3 months +)

#### Youtuber

YouTube

Dec 2020 - Present (3 months +) https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCGElw\_z7TYP35Z4AQcdT2dw

## Data Entry Operator

Income Tax Department of UK Mar 2020 - Present (1 year +)

#### **Education**



#### Adarsha Pre Cadet School

SSC

2020 - 2022

#### Adarsha Pre Cadet School

**JSC** 2019 - 2019

#### **Skills**

```
Html • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Logo Design • Python (Programming Language) •
Adobe Photoshop • Adobe Illustrator • .NET Framework • Bootstrap • Unity(game engine)
```